prameg.com 2012-10-23

# Privacy Policy

**WorldsLastChance.com** (" **WorldsLastChance.com** ", "we", or, "us") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information, and providing a safe and secure environment for our users. For that reason, we follow a privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") that applies to our web site (the "Site") and our distribution of various newsletters. As part of our Privacy Policy, we want you to understand what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit the Site and when you receive e-mails from us, how we may use that information, whether we will disclose it, and how you can correct the information. Our Privacy Policy applies to visitors who browse the materials on our site and to users who choose to register with **WorldsLastChance.com** and become "Members". Please note that by using the Site, you signify your agreement with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here and indicate the date on which the Privacy Policy was updated so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it. Your continued use of the Site after any changes to the Privacy Policy will mean that you have accepted these changes.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to the Site and our distribution of our Newsletters, and not to other websites to which we may link. 

_**Security**_ **WorldsLastChance.com** uses reasonable security methods to protect the data that resides on our server[s]. However, no security system is impenetrable. **WorldsLastChance.com** cannot warrant or guarantee the security of its server[s], nor can it guarantee that information that you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to **WorldsLastChance.com** over the Internet. _**The Information We Gather and How We Use It**_ **WorldsLastChance.com** collects information from you at several different points on the Site in the manner set forth below: **1\. Member Registration and Profile**

In order to access certain information and services on the Site, a user must first become a 

**WorldsLastChance.com** member ("Member") by completing our member registration form. During the registration process you will be required to give information such as your name, e-mail address, your street address, and birth date. The information from your registration will automatically become incorporated into "Your Profile." In the "Your Profile" section of the Site, you have the option to provide further information about yourself, upon giving this information you will be earning points that you can redeem at the Store. Your profile information will be available to users on the Site to view. _**Important Information about Changing and Updating Your Member Profile**_

If your profile information changes, or if you no longer desire to be a Member, you may correct, update or remove the personal data that you provided. This can be done at the "Your Profile" page by clicking on the "Edit Your Profile" button. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within 

**WorldsLastChance.com's** databases, access logs, and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. **2\. Surveys, Contests and Quizzes**

You may have the opportunity to participate in a number of surveys on the Site. We encourage you to complete surveys so that the Site may better serve your needs. You will also be earning points from participating in such surveys. These points can be redeemed at your own discretion at the Store. We will use survey responses solely to guide us as we make improvements and enhancements to our Site. We also offer users the ability to take other types of quizzes, to increase your knowledge in the word of God.

 **3\. Send-To-A-Friend**

If you elect to use the "Send-To-A-Friend" referral service, we will ask for your friend's name(s) and e-mail address(es). 

**WorldsLastChance.com** will automatically send a one-time e-mail inviting your friend(s) to visit the Site. We will store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. _**Cookies**_

In addition to the information and materials you provide to us, like many web sites 

**WorldsLastChance.com** uses "cookies" to assist in the collection of information so that we may provide you with services customized to your interests. A cookie is a small data file containing information such as a user's login name that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

You can set up your Internet browser to reject cookies or tell you when cookies have been sent to your computer. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of the features of our Site, so we hope you'll leave them turned on.

 **WorldsLastChance.com** also uses web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs) to access **WorldsLastChance.com** cookies and in connection with the services we offer through the Site. A web beacon is a transparent image placed on a web page that sends a signal when a person visits that page. This enables us to assess the popularity and effectiveness of the materials on our Site. We may also use web beacons in connection with newsletter and other e-mails we send to our users, to let us know whether and when the e-mail was opened. No personal information is transmitted through web beacons. _ **Other Ways We Use the Information That We Gather**_ **WorldsLastChance.com** uses information obtained from its Members and other users as to enhance Members' and other users' experiences on the Site. For example, we use cookies to: (a) access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver better and more personalized services; (b) identify which areas of the Site you have visited; and (c) prevent users from voting in polls more than once. We also collect IP (Internet Protocol) addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. **WorldsLastChance.com** does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated entities. **How To Contact Us**   
Should you have any questions or concerns about the Policy, please send an e-mail to [__](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy85530%20=%20'privacy'%20+%20'@';%20addy85530%20=%20addy85530%20+%20'WorldsLastChance'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy85530%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy85530%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)_[privacy@WorldsLastChance.com](mailto:privacy@WorldsLastChance.com)_
